Guide to the Cornell University David J. Skorton presidential inauguration records, 2006.
Cornell University David J. Skorton presidential inauguration records, 2006
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University David J. Skorton presidential inauguration records, 2006.
3-15-3561
Skorton, David J.
2.2 cubic feet.
Correspondence, printed material, publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, articles, media handbooks, planning documents, proclamations, congratulatory certificates, plaques, and other records relating to David Skorton's inauguration and inaugural festivities.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, articles, media handbooks, planning documents, proclamations, congratulatory certificates, plaques, and other records relating to David Skorton's inauguration and inaugural festivities.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Skorton, David J.; Cornell University -- Presidents.; Cornell University -- Administration.; Cornell University -- Public relations.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Inauguration Planning Documents
Series II. Congratulatory Certificates
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Inauguration Planning Documents
  - Beginning Organization, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Professional Production Company, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Invitation Lists, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Inauguration Invitation and Response Cards, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Website and Data Management, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Communications and Media, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Accommodations for Inaugural Guests, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Hosts, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Meals Provided for Guests, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Confirmation/Registration Packets, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Entertainment, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Website and Data Management, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Transportation, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Volunteers, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Safety and Security, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Run of Events, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Symposium, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Processional, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Inauguration Planning and Operational Details, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Inauguration, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Rain Plan, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Printed Materials, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Printed Materials, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - More Information, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Program and poems, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Cornell Chronicle (special inauguration coverage issue) and broadsides, September 8, 2006; Folder in O/S Archives Box 44
  - Cornell Daily Sun Ad, September 2006; CD-1957
- Series II. Congratulatory Certificates
  - Bank Street College of Education, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Bard College, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Brenda N. Tobias, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Buffalo State, SUNY, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Carnegie Mellon, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Cazenovia College, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Colgate University, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - College of Mount Saint Vincent, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - The College of New Rochelle, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - College of Staten Island, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Congressman Steven Israel, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Connecticut College, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Dartmouth College, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - D'Youville College, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Dutchess Community College, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Elmira College, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Emory University, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Empire State College, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Erie Community College, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Excelsior College, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Fordham University, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Georg-August - Universität zu Göttingen, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Georgetown College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Hofstra University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Howard University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Indiana University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Iowa State University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Ithaca College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Marist College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Marymount Manhattan, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - McGill University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Michaleen's, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Michigan State University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Mercy College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Molloy College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - National Communication Association, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Nazareth College of Rochester, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - New York Chiropractic College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - New York Institute of Technology, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - New York Medical College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Norwich University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Office of Multi-Media Development and Production, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ohio State University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Onondaga Community College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Pomona College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Prairie View A&M University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Princeton University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Purchase College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Pratt Institute, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Rockland Community College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Spelman College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Springfield College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - State University of New York, Fredonia, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - St. Francis College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - St. John's University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - St. Lawrence University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - State University of New York, Cortland, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - SUNY College of Technology at Canton, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - SUNY- Institute of Technology, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - SUNY Plattsburgh, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - SUNY New Paltz, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - SUNY Sullivan, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Tompkins-Cortland Community College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Tufts University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Tsinghua University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Tulane University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - U. I. College of Public Health, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - U. C. Santa Barbara, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - University at Buffalo, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - University of California, Davis, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - University of California, Irvine, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - University of California, San Diego, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - University of Florida, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - University of Iowa, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - University of Kansas, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - University of Maryland, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - University of Maryland, Baltimore County, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - University of Oregon, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - University of Rochester, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - University of Southern California, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - University of Texas at Austin, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - University of Toronto, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Vanderbilt University, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Washington University in St. Louis, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Westchester Community College, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - University of Virginia, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Montana State University, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Yale University, 2006 (Box 3)
  - New York University, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Wagner College, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Harvard University, 2006 (Box 3)
  - The Rochester Democrat and Chronicle, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Cathedral Corporation, Department of Agriculture and Markets, Gaston Corporation, 2006 (Box 3)